So now that we understand tasks, what comes next?
现在我们已经对任务有所了解了 接下来是什么呢？
>> Well, then you actually start to get drawing the screens.
接下来你就可以开始绘制页面了
You get to pick up the pen, or the white board marker, or the mouse and
你可以拿起笔、白板笔或鼠标
start trying to imagine what these scenes,
开始想象用户互动的
these environments the user's going to interact with actually look like.
那些场景和环境究竟是怎样
So you're going back to the tasks and
然后你回到任务
kind of figuring out what are the pieces of information that they need to see.
然后寻找用户需要知道的信息
What are the pieces of information they need to provide.
任务当中需要提供哪些信息
How do those all fit together on the screen to support that task?
页面上的这些信息组合起来会如何支持这个任务？
And from there you can kind of start building one screen and
在这个基础上 你可以开始制作包括这个任务的一个页面
maybe a couple of screens that cover that task.
或者几个页面
And then look for connections.
然后寻找之间的联系
You can start looking for things that happened earlier to the user,
一开始 可以找一找之前用户是如何行动的
that brought them to this stage.
是怎么来到当前阶段的
You know, those screens want to be related in some way.
你知道的 这些页面都需要通过一定方式联系起来
Or you think about things that they want to do from
或者你要考虑一下在当前这个时间点
that point once they complete that task, well where do they go?
他们完成任务之后会做什么 会去哪儿？
And as you start to kind of get all these screens you start to build these
你完成这些页面之后
flows and connect them.
你就要开始制作流程 把它们联系起来
You have a sense of which things are really important which things are less
你应该知道哪些是非常重要的
important or frequently used.
哪些没那么重要 哪些使用较多
You start to build out the structure for this experience.
要开始构建这种体验的结构
And you think about the user might come in this way and spend a lot of time here
同时 还要考虑用户可能通过这种方式过来 在这里待不少时间
and then hop over into this different condition and spend time there.
然后进入其他地方 在那里待些时间
That starts to guide you about how the overall navigation of that experience
这样就能让你知道
is going to work.
体验的整个流程
>> And which tool do you love to use to do that?
做这项工作的时候 你喜欢用什么工具呢？
>> I love paper and pencil.
我喜欢纸和笔
>> Right.
是的
>> But at some point you get more and more detailed with what you're doing.
但某个时候开始你需要做得越来越具体
So you can start very coarse.
一开始的时候非常粗糙
You can just start with a white board or
可以就是一个白板
scraps of paper because you want to kind of fail quickly.
或者是几张纸 因为你想要比较快地失败
You want to draw out things, realize what's wrong with them,
你想要画出些东西 发现有什么错误
crumple them up, and throw them away.
然后捏起来丢掉
And draw them again.
然后再画
A lot of what I do as a designer is iteration.
作为设计师 我经常做的事情就是迭代
And there's a saying that writing is rewriting,
有人说写作就是重写
that applies to design as well.
对设计来说也一样
>> Right. >> Design is redesigning.
— 是的 — 设计就是重新设计
>> So you design it to show it to someone, you get some feedback, and
所以 你设计出来 给某些人看 得到反馈
then you redesign it.
然后重新设计
>> Yeah, absolutely.
当然可以
And you often will draw a lot of different things.
你经常会画很多不同的东西
And just kind of get a feel for, from feedback and from your own experience,
可能是在各个其他的步骤中
and from the understanding of the user that you've built up through all those
从反馈、从自身经历、从对用户的理解
other steps.
得到的一种感觉
Which ones are the best bets, which make the most sense?
哪些东西更好呢？
And some of that is about making a choice based on the whole product.
有时候还需要在整个产品的层面做选择
It's good if you can get to a smaller number of patterns that the user has to
用户需要学习的模式越少越好
learn rather than the user having to learn 100 different styles of
比那种用户需要学习 100 种不同的方式
working with your app.
来使用应用要好得多
>> Right.
是的
So when do I know that I'm done with all these checks?
所以我什么时候才能完成所有的检查？
>> Okay. So you're never done.
好的 永远不会完成
That's a joke.
玩笑 玩笑
That's design. >> Oh that sounded unfortunate.
— 这是设计 — 听上去很不幸呢
>> No sorry.
不好意思
>> Okay. >> I mean it's great you could try but
— 好的 — 我觉得你尝试去完成是很好的
you're never going to quite get there.
但是你无法真正地完成
Like there's always going to be something that you want to change.
你总会有想要去变更的东西
You learn something else from the testing or from putting it out.
你从测试或者发布中学到了什么
Or there's some new capability that comes around that you
或者是你发现有些新的能力
want to incorporate into the product.
想加入到产品中去
You'll get closer and closer.
你会越来越接近
You'll continue to approach it, but you'll never quite land there.
你会持续地向目标走去 但是你不可能真正地完成
So you'll kind of go through and you'll iterate, and you'll redesign, and
你就是不断改进 迭代 重新设计
you'll go to higher and higher levels of fidelity.
然后得到保真度越来越高的原型
You'll go from those pencil sketches to mockups to very polished mockups to
从一开始用笔画出的草图 到模型 到非常精细的模型
prototypes.
再到原型
And you'll start building it at some point.
然后在某个时间点你就要开始制作
So that said, there's things you can look for.
所以说 你一直都有要做的事情
>> Okay. >> You don't have to give up all hope.
— 好的 — 不要放弃所有的希望
>> So,
— 好的 — 那
have you covered all of those tasks that you want to address, right?
你有没有提供你想要解决的所有任务？
Have you completely solved the problem you were looking at?
你有没有完全解决你一开始想要解决的问题？
Does the product have a point of view about what things are important and
对于哪些比较重要哪些不太重要
which aren't?
产品有没有清晰的概念？
You know, if you have the tasks that are high priority make them feel like
如果你有需要强调的
they're important to the user.
对用户非常重要的任务
Like stress them so that they know this is what this product is about.
要强调这个任务 让用户知道这个产品是做什么的
You've done user testing, right?
你已经做过用户测试 是吧？
>> Of course >> Okay, so
— 当然 — 好的
have you covered all of the issues that arose from that?
所以你有没有解决测试中发现的所有问题？
Have you kind of addressed those high priority items?
有没有解决首要的一些项目？
And then finally, have you solved the problem you set out to solve?
最后是 你有没有解决一开始你想要解决的问题？
You go back to those original goals and
你要回到最初的目标
see am I actually meeting what I understand I need to do for that user?
我有没有做到一开始我认为应该为用户做的东西？
>> And what would be a good mark or signal to tell me that I need to move
有没有什么明显的标志或信号告诉我
from design to actually do rapid prototyping or stuff like that?
我需要从设计阶段进入到快速原型设计阶段之类的？
>> You should do that as rapidly as you can.
你应该尽早地进入这个阶段
You know, even if you're just testing things on paper Prototyping it out.
即便你只是对纸面原型进行测试
Using kind of the simplest tools that you can do.
使用最简单的工具
You have that analysis phase and then once you move into design,
你都有个分析阶段 一旦你进入设计阶段
you know design and prototyping should be very much hand in hand.
你就知道设计与原型设计该是同时的
The closer you get to something that feels like a real experience to a user,
你向用户提供更真实的体验
the better feedback you're going to get from them.
你就会得到更好的反馈
>> Of course. >> In many cases.
— 当然 — 在很多情况下
So, you want to get to that point as rapidly as you can.
所以 你需要尽快地到达这个阶段